Let's now take this to the metros and keep creating
friends. In the previous video of the Quantity Banaras series,
we did a comparative analysis of the cost of many sectors - 16,
footwear, banking, pet and sheet for chemical
IT. He did not sit for watching friends. The
biggest and leading companies of the white goods and auto ancillary sector.
If you have
not seen that video yet, then click on the link of that, which is
coming in the add button. In today's
video, while continuing the series, I will compare
some selected market leading sectors of the life insurance sector.
I hope you like this series
very much and will look at the chances of all these sectors
one by one. You are getting many
user names and then for your
long-term interest in love, if
you have any active stop these suggestions or
any recommendations, then message it in the format
so that in the upcoming videos, we can
gradually include staff from the existing sectors
in our Banaras. Friends, if you have
not subscribed to my channel, then do it now
and the bell icon is for it because we
Similarly, we keep discussing many interesting videos
and topics, so it is
very difficult for you to make your
decision because we can make it even better
and this is our mission from you, so without
taking any more updates and let's get
started friends, all these are the quantity
parameters on which we will qualify all these cards, the
fundamental parameters of all these businesses,
Anil Ice Cream and compare them, in this
you have
seen pictures of many leaders, whose discussion I will do one by one,
but from many old
pap o meter, that is, all those staff have
commented on their same card above meter,
in this we have discussed all the sectors of this stage,
when Banaras, then we have discussed their
quantity parameters in detail,
quite late, I will
not do the details of all those positive parameters here specifically, but the new
parameters which are
more relevant for this chapter specific to the gas sector, I will do a
little discussion on them in lunch
so that you can get some idea about all these
card parameters, radio parameters, so
I have Chinese suit all these card and
girls  For tester's nurse
contact number results, let's start with
market operations. Overseas market
operations are large, so this company has some
competitive advantages. The bigger the
market complex, the more it will get
here. There will be various types of eyes and I am doing
35 toxic comparative nurses in the
life insurance sector. In that, the first
stock is HDFC Life, the second is Kasba Life, and the
third is ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance. So, now according to
marketability, the biggest
company is Adidas Slide, which gets postman recruitment,
and the smallest companies are
Kshetra Life Insurance, which gets that end, and one is this. If we
look at it according to revenue size, then go
here and turn it over to Post
and here ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance was the first 93, which gets
28798 government, under its business, your
smallest company in times to produce
size is seen in HDFC Life, which is
given a little bit.
If we talk about profit size, then here we have to consider the
size of this company according to this.
There, A proof was coming first, but in
IAS proof, here you can see that the
life insurance business of ICICI Prudential is
not that profitable compared to other top companies. A lot of their underwriting is done, a
lot of their profits are lost on claim settlement, that is a
glimpse of their underwriting process, a lot of it is just
not underwriting pass, compared to the
players, here we are talking relative,
I am not giving this point in any episode,
their underwriting is very
thick, but if we do a relative comparison with
HDFC Life, then you can see that
their profit is a little less. Since IAS
Life is a profitable company in terms
of profit after tax, the
protection of facial is less, then SBI
Life comes at Rs 1422 crore because the
value of profit after tax is given to the cost range
and the score of the team, second step
comes HDFC Life and third rank is IAS
proof of Rs 1070 crore, its property
tax financial year was done, it was a little difficult.
Who gets one, then let's talk about the
effectiveness of criminal, how strong is the company, that is
badla stang-stang, its revenue
compound word sorry, here it has been done at a low level, on the
first time, a life in
contact person is very strong,
saying Ravinder, sixteen percent of almost 60% of land,
car, he is from Australia, by the way,
exceptionally good values ​​from numbers
posts from China,
on checking the straight stitching, here comes ICICI Pru Life
Insurance, he was in second hand to school, it
also has a very decent, very good
number of 14.8 percent, when it is saying
its little driver comes SBI Life,
its alternative and proximity,
very fast setting, these three numbers, but
still if we compare, then its
best numbers are looking at the important
percentage, what to do with revenue of almost 14%,
he gets a little thing, so
this is about Ravinder Kaur, now let us talk about
how much will be the profit house and the
profit, if I have to show you that
ICC  Cricket is taking a huge hit, it is
making a profit of only 2.8%, so
now the actual profit inflow from these other two players has been
much less than the other two peers,
definitely not very impressive, 2.5
%, what will you do with its profit in the last 10
years, not at all very impressive, third you
get one thing and the
most profitable company by subscriber number is like this,
in the memory of fast track court three,
profit language of 98%, definitely very impressive, very
strong, now quick tips
company HTC is saying that changed Tennison
shared on this and we already
discussed this in many videos, on the last issue
I had made a dedicated video in which
market Aamir talked about
how much difference does the market meter make
and what is its fundamentalism, what is sugar,
so in front of them it was also discussed
that airline companies are the most
important prime factor behind stock
price compounding, so speed is less,
Pandey is good, strong, turmeric field and
increasing  There is tension in the Congress
list, for the sake of press, catch-up is competing
in alone grand and we will see that in the future also
in this country comparison, but
you can check the numbers, the highest
number is from this, negative numbers from this, so
you can see this in the rate of office,
such enemy light, which is based on number - 2.7 per
cent and which is given the third rank,
cost and here
SBI Life comes for the second time, HDFC
Life, both have very important numbers,
around 14%, but still if we
compare with number 11, the state allied forces
person is done something, but the market
value is hundred percent, voting percent,
with the base company, the last second
hand is received from SDM,
value of new bridges margin, this is a very
important tool which is
specifically used in the life insurance sector, it
shows whether the
business is coming to it or how much margin the
company is able to create and business, so the
higher this number, it
helps the company to grow a lot, this business
man.  Acquire new customers, then you
can see ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance's subscribe number six. The
baby margin of the 2017 operation
is, first, Metro, three, who gets it,
second, you get HDFC Life, its number is
part of it, so such points, almost
medicine's disease, second hand, and then
who gets such side, and third, you get Paper
Ras Malai, its numbers are quite Edison, no
number, but still if you compare
Ink Jet numbers, then there is a little
spread here, its one comes to it, on third man, one is
given with notty at 40
percent of PNB margin numbers. Now let's talk about
small man bus stand ratio. This is also very
important because it shows
how long customers stay.
They sign up for a life insurance
policy, its quality continues. As long as
customers do it, there is long term retention
and stability. You get to know
which company is doing business with which
company's service. This is how satisfied the customer is
and you can make long term plans
because life insurance.  Insurance business is
quite long-term. If you
do premium, then usually you keep
doing it for 25-35 years, so therefore there will be
persistence, consistency and
retention. So, if you look clearly at this note specified
future and business in parties, then
you have to see clearly that on post dated check
out, the formal number of HDFC Life is 92.98,
almost 90%, that is the persistence
end because it needs 31.7 because
who gets to turn the flashlight and the
rest of the number, Seven Computer Lab Life is a
tool of HDFC Life, the number is much less than the number
and is much less than HDFC Life,
you have to keep in mind that
some of the fundamental parameters of the strange light should be very
strong and on that basis, if we
compare it with the unknown number, then the second
wife, husband, wife comes, the deposit percentage of almost a
different person's
presidency is secrets, the Third Reich
with the number of 20%.  If you want to live an approved life,
offer it to her and one is given to her.
Now if we talk about holidays in the finance
sector, then we will check the numbers of the accused, return on equity,
electronic products given as return gift to the accused,
they will be travelled, so
if you look at the numbers of the accused here, then
HDFC Life is the best among the best numbers, it
gets first 93 percent marks, the
army's number of 20.51 is definitely very
impressive, SBI Life comes
second, who gets the second, finally here it is
4.9 percent, definitely a very impressive
number but not very interesting,
compared to Dadar peers, so accordingly you
can see from this, where is the life insurance,
but a little one has been given to this, please note that
50% of the army's return on
equity, now we will talk about the promoter
plus institutional holding, this company has
more, these numbers are high, so
you so that from health to complete
deposit, shoes of government etc. are good, the
promoters have invested in all these things
Detailed discussion of mysterious that has been done in the first few
videos, so if you
want to understand a little more discussion that these
parameters are very important, promoter
holding is your important for
institutional liquid water and
why I always take time for
comparative analysis of both of these, so you can understand a little
more detailed medical why this contest
parameter is important in this post, the
points that I have given, you will see the most
impressive number that happened with such chapter life
insurance, 96.4 portion problem
system Noida Authority on the top job, you
can see that when this number is above 90% then
I am quite impressed, it seems quite strong, 80%
above number seems quite
decent to me, it seems comfortable and I
look for a minimum above 70%, if
this number is above 70% then I find it a little okay, otherwise I
refer to ADO 90%,
you can see that in all three staff,
promoters reaction holding is quite
strong and that is 20%  These are the numbers of all three,
but still if we compare the exact numbers then the
cost price rate question
comes. Next portion of the book introduction will be
found
with the number of 0.1 per cent since then and finally
third is HDFC Life 1948 with
almost 98% number 7 button. As mentioned, the
numbers of these teams are very strong,
but then the jack numbers are low, so
make it accordingly and you can see that
baking powder is definitely like that of those who arrest pollution. Its
discussion is done in great detail, why, after
seeing those descriptions in earlier videos, I already
consider it important in activation, but destroyed
with only thing that I should consider,
hence I have considered this version as an
important metric, but in unison with together with other
factors, I have considered
this is not done till date, this will be a problem,
but still if you
can see it according to the current generations, then you will see that
whatever fennel  Undervalued stocks that are left
expensive will be better off and they will
get better returns. Stocks that were slightly overvalued
here will be
given a small penalty, their returns will be reduced slightly,
and their returns will also be reduced slightly. So, you
can see this. This is present
here. True Life
Insurance's current rate is a little low compared to the rate of
57.8%.
If we compare it with all
other stocks, the valuation is slightly lower. But still, you
can see that life insurance is a little
undervalued in general because the business is
a little underrated and has a good growth potential in
India. Therefore,
life insurance customers have some return
value, they invest. But still, if we complete
these three, then the highest
valuation is of HDFC Life and the
lowest valuation is of ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance. Accordingly, the first bank
ICICI Prudential Life is given
because it is the most undervalued topic. It
gets the Frankfurt 3 thing and the highest
expense valuation, meanwhile,
investors are watching HDFC Life.  Life
ranks it third and keeps doing a kiss. Now let's talk about
how much stock
price compounding this company has shown in the last 100
years. Stop at scan hot Pandey grocery
here. The camp is hanging here. The subscribe
numbers of HDFC Life are looking
at 4.8 percent. That shift percentage is quite
good. This company has one and a half slides.
It gets the team key. If you
check the number of SBI Life Care, then its
second hand comes. Airport cent percent
is soft computing and I took shampoo
here for a while, it gets one thing that is
3.6 percent of the top 10 companies
with strangers. So in summary, if we talk
friends, here all the three numbers are quite
decentralized, but the office which is here
and performs well, we have a hair oil Hamdard.
HDFC Life has strengths
with an aggregate of 70%. HDFC Life goes on the post
but the companies which come, the
business which comes to it, SBI
Life with 6.7 percent kits and
finally  A pool of interest for me shows
fat 40% that I will get something. So from now on
you can understand
which company will perform on the basis of quantity face on the trade fair meter
and which
country under phone, lie behind.
Now youngsters players will miss you. So
this discussion is about making all these contracts, that is,
in the film box, all your
staff, these things, stars, paste of
computational skip, this will give you a lot of useful
flats. If you are in the life insurance
sector and I also believe that
you should keep exposure in the life insurance sector, it has
low penetration. In future,
whenever the investment of pregnant investors of India will increase in its final add,
then now the real life insurance
will benefit from it, so
you can get some benefit from life insurance
if your investment from work is
process plate. So if you
want to invest in the life insurance sector in India, then these three
stars, Computer Banaras, which we have done, will be
beneficial for you. Another
important discussion.  But use it to your
long-term interest in thought process, this is
my hope, left this side discussion will be
used, so this was today's video, this is
Knowledge Power Supreme, this channel
is commissioned to bring the right thing to you,
in the upcoming videos we will discuss many things related to mutual fund
investing, asset allocation and desktop
and will
discuss many interesting topics, so
definitely subscribe to the channel
and email that, please share if
you liked this video, if
you feel that this information
can help someone, then
share it with your friends and family members
and subscribe to the channel, we will see
you in the next video
with another coffee discussion, till then take care of
tears, Papa